http://www.familyplanning.net/en/privacy-policy

Menu
HomeFamily of the AmericasAbout usBoard of DirectorsCore BeliefsHistoryFamily and youth congressesIn Defense of Life and FamilyClergy & Religious SupportInfluencing Government LeadersInfluencing Medical ScienceThe Ovulation MethodOverviewChart your CycleReproductive PhysiologyAchieving PregnancyPostponing PregnancyBreastfeedingSpecial Circumstances (discontinuing Artificial Birth Control)Endorsements of The MethodArmand M. Nicholi, Jr., M.D.Janet E. Smith, Ph.D.
The Late Prof. Jerome LejeuneThe Late Walker Percy, M.D.Scientific SupportStatistical StudiesScientific ResearchRecent StudiesWhy Natural is Better Than Artificial?Let us CompareArtificial Methods of Birth ControlFemale and Male Sterilization Causes Serious ConsequencesAbortion can Cause Cancer and Heart DiseaseWho Protects Women from Cancer?Normal Breast Physiology and Breast Cancer RiskEffects of Artificial, Methods on FertilityCord Blood: Who owns it?Around the WorldPeople's Republic of ChinaPhoto GalleryGetting InvolvedWish to become a Teacher?Donate Now!Master Teacher Institute TrainingsUpcoming EventsProductsMaterialsDownloadablesVideos
You are hereHome
Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form.
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
- To improve our website
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
- To improve customer service
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
- To process transactions
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
- To send periodic emails if you agree to receive them
The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.
After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.
Do we use cookies?
We do not use cookies.Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.
California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.
Online Privacy Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. www.familyplanning.net
5929 Talbot Rd.
Lothian, MD 20711
USAfafmercedes@yahoo.com
This policy is powered by Free Privacy Policy and Rhino Support helpdesk software.
Blog Archive
All blog posts
2017 [1]March [1]
Contact Us
Phone: 301-627-3346 (out of EE.UU.)
E-mail: info@familyoftheamericas.org
Copyright © 2014 Family of the Americas
DONATE NOW!
Contributions are tax deductible. We are dedicated to educating and strengthening women and families worldwide. FAF was founded in 1977 for the purpose of promoting programs for the family.  If you want to donate:Please mail to: 5929 Talbot Rd. Lothian MD 20711
Donate here
Donate via PayPal
Stay Connected
Subscribe to Family of the Americas monthly eNews to learn what’s happening in our community
Email *
Suscríbase
Subscribe to Family of the Americas monthly eNews to learn what’s happening in our community
Email *
Spread our MISSION
The natural method in
your smartphone!
Home
Privacy Policy
